[Music]
life reduced just to swiping left and
right. Scrolling through the void in the
pale blue light balls light up like a
deck of cards. Left it at the bottom
hiding all our scars.
Chase me through another night. It's
easier to scroll to try to make it
right. Everyone's performing. No one
wants the truth. Chasing validation just
another year.
Schwe up reality fitting into screech.
Matching with a ghost or another
connection is a slow validation hit in
the dark pretending we exist. Wo wo wo
wo wo. 50 hearts on hold. Wo wo wo wo
wo. Dump a be of gold.
I'm just another pixel in a cynical
parade. Tapping out confession to a
digital charade. Filters all my feelings
and the fire is cliche. We chase another
stranger just to fill the day. We never
look up from the glare. Lost in the beat
we share. Wasting days in disrepair.
Do you even care?
Reality fitting into streets. You with
the drug store and under me
validation hits. We're both in the dark
pretending we exist. Wo wo wo wo wo.
Empty hearts on hold.
Don't be so cold.
[Music]
[Applause]